上帝
Oh, my god.
在我喝过的咖啡里
This is quite possibly the worst coffee
这个恐怕是最难喝的
I've ever tasted.
这味道让我印象深刻
It's actually kind of fascinating.
像是猴子尿混着电瓶水
It tastes like a monkey peed in battery acid.
你今天就没有新书发售或其他事做吗
Don't you have a book coming out today or something?
有  怎么啦
Yeah. So?
怎么啦  你这样盯着我写报告
So? You are watching the paperwork.
相当怪异
It's creepy.
你难道没有别的地方可去了吗
Don't you have somewhere else to be?
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
天啊  我知道了
Oh, my gosh. I get it.
你在逃避
You're hiding.
今天你的新书发售  你躲在这儿
Your book is coming out today, and you are hiding.
不  躲避是要用被子筑起堡垒
No, hiding would be building a fortress out of my comforter
再喝上许多苏格兰威士忌
And then downing a fifth of scotch,
不过显然这样有害健康
But apparently that's considered unhealthy
我原以为你不在意别人的想法
I thought that you don't care what people think.
是不  太在意
I don't... Much
贝克特  好  马上到
Beckett. Yeah. Right on my way.
发现尸体
A dead body?
太棒了
Yes!
就是这家伙吗
That's the guy?
-听说了  -大家都听说了
- You heard, huh? - Oh, everyone's heard.
你真的把贝克特探长
You really base your next character
作为下本书的原型吗
On Detective Beckett?
每个艺术家都需要一位女神
Every artist needs his muse.
再叫我女神
Call me a muse again,
我就打断你的腿  懂吗
And I will break both your legs, ok?
懂了
Okay.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
杰克·里弗特和哈尔·莫里森
Jack Livert and Hall Morrison.
他们搬进来的时候
When moving in,
在垃圾箱里
They saw a worn out rug,
发现一张废弃的地毯
Sticking out at a dumpster
他们原以为今天很走运
They figured it's their lucky day;
但带回家后  大惊失色
They bring it home, only to find surprises inside.
地毯居然裹着尸体
Dead guy in a rug?
我们很自然的想到了你
Naturally we thought of you.
是的
Yeah.
点38口径  近距离射击  当场死亡
38 calibers, close range, killed him instantly.
有身份证件吗
You got an ID?
没有  口袋是空的
No, pockets were empty.
没有钱包  没有钥匙  也没有首饰
No wallet, no keys, no jewellery.
我们认为是劫杀
We figured a robbery gone wrong.
-这不是抢劫   -这不是抢劫
- This wasn't a robbery. - This wasn't a robbery.
如果我要抢劫
I rob someone, I'm not gonna stick
可不会把尸体包好再扔掉
Around to wrap them up and throw them away
血迹喷溅形态表示
Blood spatter indicates
他被射杀时站得离地毯很近
He was standing near the rug when he was shot.
尸体在哪里发现的
Where did they find this?
东三街  离这儿两个街区
East 3rd, about two blocks away.
好  让鉴定科的人来处理地毯
Alright, let's get SUC on the rug.
纤维  血迹  能识别的痕迹
Fibers, blood, identifying marks.
派一组去垃圾箱看看
Also get a team to the dumpster,
看能不能挖出点什么来
See if they can dig anything else up.
-蕾妮  查查他的身份  -收到
- Lanie, see if you can find an ID. - Got it
不用了
Don't bother.
我知道他是谁
I know who he is.
灵书妙探
第一季第四集
发现什么了吗
You got something?
杰夫·霍恩  48岁  两届市议会议员
Jeff Horn, 48, 2 terms City Council Member.
你朋友吗
Friend of yours?
我在公交车的广告上看到过他
I recognized him from the bus ads...
他在竞选连任
He's running for reelection.
消息会传得满城风雨
The press is gonna be all over this.
-他有家人吗  -有
- He has a family? - Yeah.
得赶在狗仔队之前通知他的家人
Well, let's try to notify 'em before the jackals do.
霍恩夫人  我知道这很难
Mrs. Horn, I know this is difficult,
但还是要问
But when was the last time
你和丈夫最后一次联系是什么时候
You heard from your husband?
昨晚11点我给他打了电话
I called him last night around 11:00
他刚刚结束竞选筹资
He was finishing up a fund-raiser
准备回到办公室
And heading back to the office.
他总是工作到这么晚吗
Did always work that late?
竞选期间是这样
During elections.
他认为  即使在竞选期间
He believed that it was a politician's obligation
政治家的责任也是
To get the people's work done,
把大家的事情做好
Even while running for office
如果他彻夜不归呢
And when he didn't come home?
他经常整晚不回家
Well, it wasn't unusual for him
在办公室的睡沙发
To crash on his couch instead of coming home,
但是  当弗兰克今天早上打来电话
But...when Frank called this morning--
弗兰克
Frank?
弗兰克·内斯比特  杰夫的竞选经理人
Frank Nesbit, um, Jeff's campaign manager.
昨晚你丈夫的声音是怎么样的
How did your husband sound last night?
你指什么
What do you mean?
他有没有不安  好像出了什么事
Did he seem troubled, like there was something wrong?
没有  他听起来很开心
No, he seemed happy.
这根本讲不通
It doesn't make any sense.
他是个好人  一个好父亲
He's a good man and he's a good father,
他每天出门
And every day he would go out there
都尽力让这个城市更美好
And try to make this city a better place every day.
他就这么走了
And for him to die like this...
不  我该怎么跟女儿们说呢
Oh, no. What am I supposed to tell my girls?
你还好吧
You okay?
很好  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
通知家属噩耗很不容易
Can't be easy breaking that kind of news.
没错  那个
Yeah, well...
谢谢你没有以此来取笑我
Thanks for not making it a joke.
我是滑头  可不缺心眼
Hey, I'm a wiseass, not a jackass.
我觉得没什么区别
I didn't know there was a difference.
下一步打算怎么办
So what's your next move?
找他生前最后见的人  还是做行程表
Last person to see him alive? Establish a time line?
吃点甜甜圈  还是更难喝的咖啡
Grab a doughnut? More really bad coffee?
你写的那个女警官
This, um, female detective of yours,
到底有多少成分取材于我
Exactly how much will she be based on me?
她不太聪明  还有点放荡
Well, she's not too bright and kind of slutty.
好吧  那她是滑头还是缺心眼呢
Right. So was that wiseass or jackass?
实际上  她缺心眼
Actually, that was jackass.
不  老实说  你根本没必要
No, honestly, you're not gonna have
为此感到尴尬
Anything to be embarrassed about,
她聪明过人
She's gonna be... She's gonna be really smart,
破案经验丰富  花容月貌
Very savvy, haunting good looks,
工作做得得心应手
Really good at her job...
也有些放荡
And kind of slutty.
卡塞尔
Castle--
我得接个电话
I should really get that.
-你好  -亲爱的  我
- Hello? - Oh, sweetheart, I--
妈妈  慢点说  出什么事啦
Whoa, mother, slow down. What's wrong?
我就想确认一下你现在还好吗
I just wanted to make sure you were all right
我怎么会不好呢
Why wouldn't I be all right?
没有一个人买你的新书
No one is buying your book.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我现在在书店里面
I am standing in the middle of the bookstore,
没有一个人在买你的书
And no one is buying your book.
好吧  你在书店干什么
Okay. What are you doing in a bookstore?
我饿了  进来买馅饼
I was hungry. I-I came in for a pastry.
都在那边  你的书
And there they were, all your books,
都只是摆着
Just... Sitting there.
那些书两小时前才上架
Well, they only just went on sale two hours ago.
你期待读者大排长龙吗
What did you expect, a line out the door?
哈利·波特上一集发售时就大排长龙
There was one for the last Harry Potter.
不过德里克·斯道姆又不是哈利·波特
Yes, well, uh, Derrick Storm is not Harry Hotter.
看得出来
Clearly.
没有一个人来买吗
No one's bought one?
等等  孩子  稍等
Hang on, kiddo. Hang on.
没有
No.
-你还好吧  -是的
- You okay? - Yeah.
我才不管是否免费
I don't care if it was free.
就算给我钱  我也不会要那地毯
Even if you pay me, I'm still not gonna take that rug.
你说你一直在纽约生活
You're telling me you lived in New York your whole life,
却从来没当过马路杀手
And you never scored a piece of roadkill?
马路杀手
"Roadkill"?
这招大家都用  老兄
It's an accepted practice, bro.
有什么旧东西不要了
When you're done with your old stuff,
就扔在街头  留给运气不好的的人
You leave it on the street for those less fortunate--
艺术家  学生  原对冲基金经理
Artists, students, former hedge fund managers.
把滴入经济学的作用发挥到极致
It's trickle-down economics at its finest.
好吧  不过我可不想当抚恤对象
Yeah, well, I prefer not to be trickled.
你还记得我那张红色沙发吗
You know that red couch I have,
你最爱的那张
The one you like so much?
不会吧  老兄
Don't you say it, bro.
在54街和莱克星顿街那片儿
54th and Lex.
真恶心
That's gross.
太恶心了
Gross.
再也不去你家玩麦登橄榄球(电子游戏)了
We are never playing Madden at your place again.
-警官  -怎么了
- Detective? - Yeah?
你刚刚才进去啊
You just got in there.
老天
Aw, Jeez.
纽约州  杰夫里·艾伦·霍恩
NEW YORK STATE- HORN, JEFFREY ALLEN
杰夫里·霍恩
Jeffrey Horn.
干的好  斯科特
Nice work, Scott.
好的  埃斯波西托
Yeah. Esposito
不  查查他的通话记录
No, run l.u.d.s on his phone.
看看除了他妻子  还和谁通过电话
See if he talked to anyone other than his wife.
他们找到钱包了
They found the wallet.
钱和信用卡都不见了
Money and credit cards were gone.
弃尸现场周围有发现吗
Anything from the neighbors?
跟平时一样  猫叫
The usual--wailing cats,
电视声很大  汽车的警报
Loud tvs, car alarms.
没听见枪声  没有溅落血迹
No shots, though, and no blood spatter.
一个真正的抢劫犯
A real robber would have left the
会把钱包扔在现场
Wallet where he killed the guy.
而不是弃尸的地方
Not where he moved him.
虽然处理的很马虎
It's a sloppy cover-up,
但能得出一个结论
But it does sound one thing.
是有预谋的谋杀
This was premeditated.
麻烦你  纽约警局凯特·贝克特探长
Excuse me. Detective Kate Beckett, NYPD.
我们想见弗兰克·内斯比特
We're looking for Frank Nesbit.
霍恩的竞选经理人  有劳了
Horn's Campaign manager. Thank you.
莱恩能回避一下吗
Ryan, could you give us a minute?
我们帮孩子们找了悲伤心理专家
We've, uh, called in grief counselors for the kids.
我知道这话经常说
I know it's a cliché,
但他对我们大家  很重要
But he meant a lot to all of us.
听上去
Well, it sounds like
他不仅仅是一个候选人
He was more than just a candidate.
我们是朋友  曾想一起改变这个世界
We were friends. We wanted to change the world.
你昨晚跟他在一起吗
Were you with him last night?
是的  到大概11点
Yeah. Until... About... I don't know... 11:00
我本想打车带他一程  不过他想走走
I offered to share a taxi, but he wanted to walk.
竞选筹资在哪里举行
Where was the fund-raiser?
在马可尼家  百老汇大街83号
Marconi's-- 83rd of Broadway.
离这儿只有几个街区
That's just a dozen blocks from here.
霍恩先生的尸体
Mr. Horn’s body
在往市中心的路上被发现
Was found all the way downtown.
他有树敌吗
Did he have any enemies?
他是个政治家
Well, he was a politician.
他的竞争对手呢
What about his opponent?
很难想像贾森·博林杰
It's hard to imagine Jason Bollinger
会做出这种事情来
Doing some this like this...
他在民意测验里领先8个百分点
He is 8 points up in the polls.
最近霍恩或者他的竞选团队
Did Horn or the campaign
有没有遭到恐吓
Receive any threats recently?
就是那些怪人  没什么特别
Just your usual crackpots. Nothing special,
如果卡尔文·克里森的恐吓信件不算的话
Unless you count hate mail from Calvin Creason.
拥有酒店和俱乐部的大亨  克里森
Creason the hotel and club owner?
拥有艾克秀姆和苏活伟业
Owns, uh, Axium and the Soho majestic.
甚至白天俱乐部里有艳舞表演
Even ran club tasty back in the day.
有那么一次
There was this one time...
下次再说吧
Story for another time.
霍恩都干了什么  打击毒品贩子吗
What did Horn do, crack down on the ecstasy dealers?
克里森在下东区买下了
Creason bought that old meat packing warehouse
做肉类加工的旧车间
On the lower east side.
他想把那儿改成酒店
He wanted to turn it into his next hip hot spot--
300个房间  清酒吧  夜总会
300 rooms, sake bar, nightclub.
居民们可不想夜间的街头
Neighbors didn't want a bunch of drunken
总有一群问题人士乱晃
B&t-ers running in the streets.
所以霍恩担任委员时把它否决了
So Horn killed it in committee.
让克里森价值几百万的地产
Leaving Creason with millions of dollars
现在变得一文不值
Of now worthless real estate.
克里森和霍恩关系是不好
Creason had a beef with Horn.
但不代表他是凶手
It doesn't mean he killed him.
也难说他不是  告辞了
Doesn't mean he didn't. Excuse me.
想知道我听说他死了以后
Want to know what I did
都做了些什么吗
When I found out that he was dead?
我点了一瓶冰凉香醇的香槟
I ordered myself a nice, cold bottle of Cris'
为世界的美好而举杯  怎么了
And toasted the sweetness of the universe, okay?
真是冷酷无情  克里森先生
That's pretty callous, Mr. Creason.
听着  我为什么要在乎  凭什么
Listen, what do I care? What do I care?
这家伙是个蠢货
This guy was such a putz,
弄得好像多盖一个酒店
Acting like if another hotel going on.
世界末日就要来了
That was gonna be the end of the world.
你知道我这一项产业
Do you have any idea what one of my
对本地经济的作用吗
Properties do for local economy.
市政府应该赞助我  而不是阻止我
This city should be paying me, not stopping me.
那么就是说你有杀人动机
So I guess we could say you had motive.
这又是哪路神仙  你是警察吗
Who the hell is he? You a cop?
-我们逮捕他  -卡塞尔
- I say we arrest him. - Castle
凭什么  你没有证据
For what? Please! You got nothing here.
如果我真想把碍事的都干掉
If I was gonna go around killing everybody
那些死尸堆积起来
That ever got in my way, there would be bodies
会高过克莱斯勒大厦(纽约地标之一)
Stacked higher than the Chrysler Building.
我不需要用杀人来解决问题
I don't need to kill anyone to bury them.
你昨晚在哪里
Where were you last night?
-我在苏活俱乐部  -证人
- I was at my club in soho. - Anybody see you?
警官  我只要出门  大家都会看见
Detective, when I go out, everybody sees me.
谢谢你  克里森先生
Thank you very much, Mr. Creason.
当然
Sure.
我想洗个澡
I want to take a shower.
-下一步怎么办  -查他的不在场证明
- Where to next? - To check his alibi.
事实上  没有这个必要
Actually, that may not be necessary.
为什么
Why not?
卡塞尔  你在干什么
Castle, what are you doing?
答应我  别讨厌我
Promise not to hate me.
-我已经讨厌你了  -很好
- I already hate you. - Fair enough.
早上在现场  我拍了照片
This morning with the body I took a couple of pictures.
你在我的犯罪现场拍照
You took photos of my crime scene?
在你生气之前
Before you get mad,
我已经发了一些给一个朋友
I e- mailed a couple of them to a friend of mine.
你还把照片传给一个朋友
You e- mailed them to a friend.
准确地说  算不上是朋友
Well, not exactly a friend.
她是我的室内设计师
She's my interior decorator.
我们也在一起过
But then we slept together,
所以我也说不清她的身份了
So I don't really know what she is now.
你到底在想什么
What the hell were you thinking?
我知道  你们一起工作
I know, right? You work together,
你们认为这会很有意思
You think it'll be fun,
但是过后却觉得尴尬
But then it always makes things weird.
这是一则真实的警示故事
It's a real cautionary tale.
我说的是尸体照片的事
I'm talking about the photographs of the body.
什么  我没有发尸体的照片
What? No! I didn't send her pictures of the body.
我给她的是地毯的照片
I sent her pictures of the rug.
我想她可能能够
I thought maybe she might be able
告诉我地毯来自哪里
To tell me where it came from,
而且  她做到了
And guess what. She did.
就是这种地毯
That's the rug.
同样的地毯
That's the same rug.
别得意
Don't gloat, okay?
那副样子很讨厌
'Cause it's really unattractive.
现在可以逮捕他吗
Now can we arrest him?
我能感觉到你  兄弟
I feel you, man.
好的
Yeah, okay.
他十二点以后才到的俱乐部
He didn't arrive at the club until after midnight.
现在怎么办  等他的律师吗
So what do we do now, wait for his lawyer to show up?
我们要跟别的线索
Actually, we follow other leads.
这个我们叫做  工作
It's something that we call "working."
别的线索  很好
Other leads? Good.
既然我们都认为  他不是凶手
Since we both know he didn't do it.
克里森
Creason?
为什么说他不是凶手
What makes you think he didn't do it?
很明显嘛  所有的证据都指向他
Isn't it obvious? All the evidence points to him.
这反而证明他不是凶手
And that somehow makes him not guilty?
他就是红鲱鱼
He's totally the red herring.
红鲱鱼
The red herring.
看起来有罪  但却是清白的
An innocent character who appears guilty.
我知道红鲱鱼的意思  卡塞尔
I know what a red herring is, Castle.
这是文学里的一种行文策略
It's a literary device used in literature.
在现实中
In real life,
有嫌疑就不放过
We don't dismiss a suspect
何况他的嫌疑很大
Just because he appears too guilty.
而且我猜  你也想抓他
Besides, I thought you wanted to arrest him.
是的  因为他是工具
Yeah, because he's a tool,
不是因为他有罪
Not because he's guilty.
他是一个百万富翁
The guy's a multimillionaire.
不会蠢到用自己的地毯
He's not gonna be dumb enough to
去包尸体
Wrap a dead body up in his own rug.
这没关系
It doesn't matter.
这些地毯为克里森的酒店特别订制的
Those rugs were custom designed for Creason's hotel,
可见他与这事有关
So we know he's connected.
-埃斯波西托  -什么事
- Hey, Esposito? - Yeah?
查查哪个房间
See what you can find on that rug--
地毯不在了
If one went missing,
什么人进去过
What room it's from and maybe who had access.
好的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
开车上路
Road trip.
你很会指使身边的男人嘛
You're very good at bossing men around.
我已经发现了
I've noticed.
你是说一切都是巧合
You're telling me that it's just a coincidence
你开香槟庆祝
That a man whose murder you celebrated
他被谋杀
By drinking champagne
而且他的尸体裹着你们酒店的地毯
Was found wrapped in a rug from your hotel?
艾克秀姆酒店的所有房间都是相同的地毯
There are identical rugs in every room of the axium.
你不能要求我的当事人
You can't expect my client to be responsible
对这些地毯的下落负责
For their whereabouts.
我当然可以
Sure I can,
只要陪审团这么说
Until a jury tells me otherwise.
你在浪费我的时间
You are wasting my time.
探长  我说过了
Detective, look, I told you exactly
我昨晚的行踪
What I was doing last night.
是的  你去了俱乐部
Right, you were at the club.
他们说  你当时进门时很显眼
They said that you made quite the entrance,
两个超模  左拥右抱
A supermodel on each arm.
是的
Yeah, you know,
上次我接受过检查了
The last time I checked,
并不是因为犯罪  不是吗
That's not a crime, is it?
不是   不过是终生难忘
No, but you know what it is? Memorable.
凌晨一点之后
Witnesses don't place you at the club
你才出现俱乐部
Until 1:00 in the morning,
而霍恩
And Horn was murdered somewhere
在夜里11点到12点之间被杀
Between 11:00 and 12:00.
问题来了
Here it comes. And...
11点到12点之间  你在哪儿
So where were you between11:00 and 12:00,
克里森先生
Mr. Creason?
我在睡觉
I was asleep.
睡觉  这借口真烂
Asleep? You are lame!
烂借口  你这人真差劲
You are so lame! You’re a lamey mclamester!
你的借口真烂
You're so l- l- lame!
大家都知道克里森先生
It's a well- known fact that Mr. Creason sleeps
从下午6点到夜里12点都在睡觉
From 6:00 p.m. To midnight in order to maintain
因为他要出席俱乐部的午夜活动
A late- night presence at his clubs.
有人能证明昨晚11点到12点
Did anyone witness you sleeping between the hours
你在睡觉吗
Of 11:00 and 12:00 last night,
克里森先生
Mr. Creason?
-克里森先生  -等会儿
- Creason--  - Hold on one sec.
没有人
No.
所以你有犯罪动机和犯罪时间
So you had motive and opportunity.
等会儿  等会儿
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on one sec. Hold on.
我没有杀他  我没有理由
I didn't kill him. I had no reason to.
他挡住你的财路了
He was in your way.
是的  但是前不久
Yeah, but... Not for long.
我已经知道他会败选了
I knew he was gonna lose the election, okay?
所以我不需要杀他
So I didn't have to kill him.
我要做的就是  等
All I had to do was wait.
你并不能百分之百肯定他会败选
You couldn't be sure that he was gonna lose the election.
不  实际上  我能确定
Yes, actually, I could.
知道贾森·博林杰吗
What do you know about Jason Bollinger,
霍恩的对手
Horn's opponent in the race?
声明准备好了吗
Is the statement ready?
麦克还在准备
Mike's still working on it.
告诉麦克  帐簿网(纽约时报旗下报纸)
Well, tell Mike that "the Ledger" web site
要在20分钟内更新
Updates in 20 minutes,
这篇声明要引起市民的
And I want my quote of outrage and sympathy
义愤和同情
In the damn article.
抱歉  出事后  全部人手都开始做准备
Sorry, it's been all hands on deck since we found out.
如果你处理不好  就有得受了
If you don't handle these things right, you get crucified.
博林杰先生  我是
Mr. Bollinger, I was--
博林杰先生是我父亲  叫我贾森
Mr. Bollinger's my father. Call me Jason.
好的  贾森
Okay, Jason.
你认识卡尔文·克里森吗
How well do you know Calvin Creason?
他为我找到一些募捐者
Ah, he threw me a couple fund- raisers.
我们见过几次面  怎么了
We met a few times. Why?
他认为你有一些
Well, he seems to think
与霍恩有关的资料
That you have some information on Horn,
这些资料能确保你在选举中取胜
Something that would guarantee you the election.
-卡塞尔  -抱歉
- Castle. - Sorry.
跟我来
Come on.
参选对手研究
Opposition research?
找了位有执照的私家侦探
Conducted by a licensed private investigator.
听着  我得强调
Listen, I want to stress that
这一切都通过律师的审查
Everything we did was completely vetted by our lawyers.
并没有违法
None of it was illegal.
我们只是试着找找
We were just trying to determine
议员先生是否有人生污点
If the councilman had any significant vulnerabilities.
你们找到了
And you found some.
是的
Oh, yes.
这就是官场  但我不是坏人
Look, politics is politics, but I’m not a bad guy.
我想  只要在民意调查中我还领先
I figured as long as I was ahead in the polls,
这些就没必要公开
There was no reason to use it.
这是那个议员霍恩
That's councilman Horn?
另一位可不是他妻子
And that is not his wife.
真佩服这位议员先生
I gotta hand it to councilman Horny.
这个年纪了  身体的灵活度真不可思议
He is incredibly flexible for a guy his age.
看这个  你做过吗
Look at that. You ever do that?
你能把这些拿一边儿去吗
Would you put those away?
我是说  他能做瑜伽或者普拉提
I'm just saying, he's gotta do yoga or pilates or something.
为什么被捉奸在床的
Why is it always the family value guys that
总是说重视家庭的人
Get caught with their pants down?
因为这个世界喜欢讽刺
Because the universe loves irony,
还有多数人都是伪君子
And because most people are hypocrites.
照片里的女孩儿在想什么呢
And what was that girl thinking,
他会为她抛妻弃子吗
That he would leave his wife and kids for her?
性别歧视
That is so sexist.
有吗
How is that so sexist?
你这么想  只是因为她是女人
You assume that just because she's a woman
所以她追求的是爱情
That she was after a relationship.
想过没  她也许只是需要性呢
Did you ever think maybe she was in it for the sex?
是的  我想过  但后来我看到了他
Yes, I did. And then I saw him.
就因为他被裹在地毯里  你就改变想法了
What was it that turned you off, that he was wearing a rug?
太快了吧
Too soon?
希望私家侦探那边能帮到忙
I just hope that the P.I. can help us.
地毯这条线断了
Yo. So the rug is a dead end.
后勤部门说
According to housekeeping,
他们上星期扔掉了很多地毯
They dumped a couple dozen of 'em last week.
一半扔进了垃圾箱
Half of 'em went into the dumpsters.
一半捐给了旧货店
Half of 'em were donated to thrift shops.
克里森的顾客对房间的要求非常高
Creason's clientele is known for being hard on rooms.
怎么了  兄弟  别这样  别这样
What? Dude, dude, not cool! Not cool!
有我的名片了吧
So you have my card.
我的私人手机号在背面
Uh, my personal cell number's on the back.
如果你有更多消息
If you have any more information...
你确定你会不受引诱吗
Are you sure I can't tempt you?
不会的  柯比先生
No thanks, Mr. Kirby.
我现在在工作
I'm on duty.
工作也无法阻止我
It never stopped me.
你当时在工作吗
You were on the job?
134年里的20年
20 years out of the 134.
当然
Of course,
那会儿  我们和警察合作
Back then we had other cops as partners,
没有二流的小说家参与
Not second- rate novelists.
是的  别提这个
Yeah, don't get me started.
不好意思  二流的
Excuse me. Second- rate?
热情熔化了钢铁  拜托
"Hot lead poured out of cold steel"? Come on.
不算是莎士比亚的
It's not exactly Shakespeare.
你能把那个放下吗
Will you put that down?
你为博林杰的竞选
How long were you working
工作多久了  柯比先生
For the Bollinger campaign, Mr. Kirby?
两个星期了  但是很有趣
Oh, a couple weeks, but it was a fun one.
这位家庭为重的先生告诉他的妻子
Mr. Family values tells his wife
得工作到很晚
He's gonna work late,
可能就睡在办公室
Probably crash at the office.
但20分钟后  他就
20 minutes later, he is...
在选区开始自己的民意测验
Polling his constituency.
那那个女孩儿呢
And what about the girl?
就我所知  给她的钱物有所值
From what I could see, she was worth every cent.
她支持他
She was a pro?
你觉得那么火辣的女孩
You don't think with a body like that
不会喜欢他的演讲  是不是
She's gonna swoon over his stump speeches, do you?
你要考虑他别的兴趣
Makes you wonder what else he had a taste for.
和后果
And what it lead to.
你有这个女孩的地址吗
Do you have an address?
只在外面见面
Strictly outcall.
妓女通常都站在街角
You know, whores used to have street corners...
现在她们有网站了
And now they have web sites.
该死  五星级水准
Damn! Those are some seriously fine 5- Star,
B等轻罪啊
Class "b" misdemeanors.
兄弟  天知地知  你知我知
Dude, between you and me,
你有没有试过
You ever pay for it?
你是在计算我的婚姻吗
Are you counting my marriages?
等等  停  就是那个女孩
Wait, wait. Stop. That’s the girl in the photos.
看看她  如果你有钱
Look at her. If I had your money
莱恩  这不是色情电话
This isn't phone sex, Ryan.
可不是只要付那几分钟
You don't just pay for the two minutes that you used.
这个800号码登记的信箱
The 800 number is registered to a P.O. Box
在别的州
From out of state.
我们要在网上追踪IP地址
We're gonna have to get cyber to track down the I.P.
找到主机
See where it's hosted.
如果IP地址也在其他州呢
Well, what if the I.P.'S out of state, too?
跟当地的邮政服务中心协调
We just coordinate with the local P.D.S.
如果可能的话
If they're willing to cooperate.
这种网站的设计就是要躲开我们
Sites like these are designed to evade authorities.
能查到的  多花点时间而已
We'll get there. Just take us some time.
或者选择简单的方法
Or you could just do it the easy way.
贵宾专线  请讲
V.I.P. Liaisons.
卡塞尔  你在做什么
Castle, what are you doing?
你好  我的名字叫理查德
Hi. My name's Richard.
我这个人很慷慨的
I'm a very generous man looking to
我想和蒂凡尼安排一次特殊约会
Arrange a very special date with Tiffany.
请给我打电话
Please give me a call on my phone,
号码是347-555-2079  谢谢
Which is 347-555-2079. Thank you.
卡塞尔  你不能这样
Castle, you can't just call
打电话约妓女
And arrange a date with a prostitute.
为什么不行
Why not?
因为我们是警察
Because we're the police.
不  不是  你们是警察
No, no, no. You're the police.
我只是一个寂寞的
I'm just a lonely,
期待约会的  上层绅士
Upscale gentleman looking for a date.
打赌我会先找到她
Bet I find her first.
哪位是里克·卡塞尔
Hey, there a Rick Castle here?
我就是
Right here.
您想把它放在哪儿呢  老板
Where do you want it, boss?
直接往前走
Straight through there.
卡塞尔
Castle?
-你会喜欢的  -不  我肯定不喜欢
- You are gonna love this. - No, I’m pretty sure I won't.
兄弟们
Guys, guys, guys.
就放这儿  很好
Yeah, just put it right over there. Perfect.
使劲儿  兄弟
Lift with your knees, man.
稍等一下  好吗
Stay here for one second, would you?
因为大家呢
Because you guys have been
对我热情之至
So wonderfully hospitable to me,
我也想聊表谢意
I just want to return the favor.
正好你们的咖啡难以下咽
And because your coffee is basically crap,
所以我送你们一台  意式浓缩咖啡机
I got you... An espresso machine.
很酷吧
How cool is that?
我的电话好像响了
I think my phone's ringing.
我不知道怎么安装
I don't know how to put this together.
这应该是送货负责的一部分吧
That's part of the delivery, right?
很好
Excellent.
我不懂
I don't get it.
如果不是克里森干的
If Creason didn't do it,
那地毯是怎么来的
Then how does the rug fit in?
凶手可能听说了
Killer probably heard about
他们两个不和
The feud between the two of them
所以想转移嫌疑  但手法太蠢
And tried to shift suspicion, which is stupid,
因为如果没有地毯
Because without the rug,
这案子看上去不过是抢劫出了岔子
It would've just looked like a mugging gone wrong.
所以他们弄巧成拙了
So by trying to look smart, they're actually being stupid.
我想你说到了人类的生活
I think you just described the human condition.
说到人类的生活
Speaking of the human condition,
贝克特探长怎么样了
How's it going with detective Beckett?
什么意思
What do you mean?
少来了  老爸  你以她做角色原型
Oh, come on, dad, you are basing a character off her.
你总是说  你必须爱着笔下的人物
And you always say you have to love your characters.
当然  她是个人物
Well, she is a character.
但只是用来研究而已  没有其他
But, uh, it's just research, nothing more.
是才怪
Yeah, I’m sure.
终于明白为什么书卖不出去了
Well... Found out why your books aren't selling.
听听这个评论
Listen to this review.
他的作品变得落入俗套
"His work has become so hackneyed, so cliché
所以我们怀疑卡塞尔先生
"That we wonder if Mr. Castle
是否会有新创意
Has anything new to say.
似乎他的魔力  如果曾经有的话
It appears the magic, if there ever was any,
早就消失了
Is long gone."
亲爱的  太差劲了  可怜
Oh, darling, I know it's awful. It's awful. I'm sorry.
往你心上插刀啊
Daggers to the heart.
时代周刊  雪城读者
"The Syracuse times reader"?
别担心
But don't you worry.
我也要写篇我的感想
I am going to write them a piece of my mind.
谁管什么魔力消失了啊
And who cares if they say the magic is gone?
哈珀·李(著名女作家)就写了一本书
Harper Lee only wrote one book.
你可写了一打呢
You've written dozens.
当然了她的是文学  但我
Of course hers was literature, but still, I...
你觉得她花多久找到那个评论
How long do you think it took her to find that review?
-可能整个下午  -对  对
- Probably all afternoon. - Yeah, yeah.
好了  知道她是疼你才这么做的吧
Oh, come on. You know she does it out of love, right?
她觉得她有责任让你觉得踏实
I mean, she thinks it's her job to keep you grounded.
我确实觉得踏实了
I certainly feel ground.
你来处理  一号
You have the bridge, number one.
-喂  -是理查德吗
- Hello. - Is this Richard?
对  哪位
Yes, it is. Who's this?
我是蒂凡尼  你打电话要约我
It's Tiffany. You called me for a date?
对 是我打的
Yes, I did,
蒂凡尼  非常高兴你打给我
Tiffany, and I am so glad you called.
只是好奇  你现在穿着什么
Just out of curiosity, what are you wearing right now?
你吓死我了
Damn, girl, you scared me.
蕾妮  你周围只有死尸而已
Lanie, you're surrounded by corpses.
对  7点之后通常都见不到活人
Yeah, I don't expect the living after 7:00.
有趣  我也是
Funny, neither do I.
我是法医  你是为什么
I'm an M.E. What's your excuse?
-别损我  -你活该
- Oh, don't be mean. - You deserve it.
下了班和我一起喝酒
Getting a drink with me after work
没和大作家一起
Instead of getting your freak on with writer boy?
他很烦人  自私又自大
Well, he is annoying, self- centered, egotistical
而且极为
And completely--
有趣
Fun.
听我的  朋友  你需要点儿乐趣
And take it from me, girlfriend, you need some fun.
我说  他能差到哪儿去啊
I mean, how bad can he be?
猜猜谁刚约了妓女
Guess who's got a date with a prostitute.
理查德  我是蒂凡尼
Richard? I'm Tiffany.
很高兴见到你  蒂凡尼  请
It's a pleasure to meet you, tiffany. Please.
真绅士
Wow. A gentleman.
我们快绝种了
We're a dying breed.
那我很幸运能发现你
Well, then it's lucky I found you.
其实是我们很幸运发现了你
Actually, it's lucky we found you.
凯特·贝克特探长
Detective Kate Beckett.
有几个问题要问你
We need to ask you some questions
是关于你和杰夫·霍恩议员的关系
Regarding your relationship with councilman Jeff Horn.
对不起
Sorry.
他是我的常客之一
He was one of my regulars,
但我发誓  他的死和我没关系
But I swear I had nothing to do with his death.
你多久和霍恩议员见一次面
How often did you see councilman Horn?
一星期一次  有时两次
Once, maybe twice a week.
开始他只是想说说话
At first he just wanted to talk.
是啊  他付你钱就是想说说话
Right. He paid you just to talk.
警官  多数男人都是因为孤独才找我
Detective, most men come to me because they're lonely,
因为身边的人不再听他们说话了
Because the people in their lives don't listen anymore.
性只是他们的沟通方式
The sex is just a way for them to feel connected again.
好  那你和霍恩议员最后一次
Okay, when was the last time
用这种方式沟通的
That you and councilman Horn connected?
两周前他来找我  整个人歇斯底里
A couple of weeks ago. He came to me hysterical.
他说他不能再来找我了
He said that he couldn't see me anymore.
怎么了  他太太发现了吗
What happened? His wife found out?
不是  另有其人
No, someone else.
他说他被勒索了
He said that he was being blackmailed.
-有人有我们的照片  -谁
- Someone had photos of us. - Who?
他不知道  他开始以为是我
He didn't know. At first, he thought it was me.
他很沮丧  惶恐不安
He got upset, and then he panicked.
他以为我告诉了我的朋友
He thought that I had told my friends.
你有没有呢
And did you?
警官 也许你也会觉得惊讶
It may surprise you, detective,
但我也有自己的梦想
But I have dreams of my own.
我只是靠这赚钱
Look, this just pays the bills.
如果我们的关系被公之于众
If our relationship ever went public,
不是只有他的生活被毁了
He's not the only one that would be ruined.
你说他  惶恐不安
You said he panicked.
对  他不顾一切要找出是谁
Yeah, he was desperate to find out who was behind it.
他想做笔交易
He wanted to cut a deal.
他说他一直付钱的话
He said that he couldn't keep making payoffs
竞选团队肯定会发现的
Without the campaign finding out.
政治  妓女  勒索
Politics, escorts and blackmail?
越来越有趣了
This just keeps gettin' better.
议员在找被谁勒索
The councilman was looking for his blackmailer.
要是他找到了会怎样
What if he found him?
他动了手  勒索的人还了手
He gets violent. The blackmailer responds.
然后为掩盖罪行就牵进克里森
Then tries covering what he's done by implicating Creason.
所以你只要找出勒索的人就行了
So all you need to do is find your blackmailer.
不可能  我把那些照片锁起来了
That's impossible. I kept those photos under lock and key.
并无恶意  贾森
No offense, Jason,
你的桌子不是诺克斯堡(美黄金储备金库)
But your desk isn't exactly Fort Knox.
如果有人知道
If somebody knew about them,
很容易就能拿到
They wouldn't be difficult to get.
你知道这个办公室
Do you know how many people
每天有多少人进出吗
Are in and out of this office?
不知道  你得给我名单
No, but I would like a list.
等等
Now wait a minute.
你想在选举还剩两周的时候
You intend on opening up an investigation
对我的竞选团队
On my campaign
进行调查吗
With two weeks left in the election?
你想干什么  让我输吗
What are you trying to do, cost me the race?
你担心什么  你没有对手了
What are you worried about? You're running unopposed.
不再是了
Not anymore.
劳里·霍恩宣布
Laurie Horn announced that
代丈夫参选
She's running for her husband's seat.
昨天我还领先8个百分点
Yesterday I had an 8- point lead.
民众同情心一上来
With the sympathy bump,
到今晚我们就会平手了
By tonight we'll be tied.
我们不能让个人的悲剧
...that we cannot let our personal tragedy
阻碍了我的丈夫
Stand in the way of my husband's vision
对未来纽约的愿景
For the future of New York.
讽刺的是  如果我现在公布那些照片
Irony is, that if I release those photos now,
人们会更加支持她
The people will love her even more.
至少有300人能拿到照片
At least 300 people had access to those photos.
你打算把他们全都审一遍吗
Are you planning on questioning all of them?
不  那只是用来做参考的
No, they're just for reference.
霍恩担心一直付钱的话
Horn was worried he couldn't keep paying
会被竞选团队发现
Without the campaign finding out.
那又怎样
So?
如果钱是来自竞选团队
So if the money was coming from the campaign,
那就一定会留下证据
Then there is bound to be a trail.
勒索
Blackmail.
我们相信他可能
We believe he may have been
用竞选经费来付的钱
Making payoffs through the campaign.
我认识杰夫很多年了
I've known Jeff for years.
他是个好人  爱家恋家
He's a good man, a family man.
你完全不知道吗
You had no idea?
不知道  如果这被公之于众
None. If this gets out...
内斯比特先生  如果他用竞选经费付钱
Mr. Nesbit, if he used campaign funds to make payments,
我们应该能够
Then we should be able to
追查出谁在勒索他
Trace them back to the blackmailer,
但我得看看你们的竞选账目
But we need access to your campaign ledgers.
当然  我给你拿光盘
Of course. I'll-- I’ll get you a disc.
但是  探长
Look, detective...
他的错误  我不是要原谅
What he did was wrong. I'm-- I'm not... Excusing it.
可一旦照片被公布
But if you release those photos,
那么他对这城市的贡献
You'll be doing irreparable harm
将不复存在
To all the good he did in this city,
更别说给他的家庭造成无法衡量的痛苦
Not to mention causing immeasurable pain to his family.
这些照片是谋杀调查的证物
These photos are evidence in a murder investigation.
不会将它们公之于众
We have no intention of releasing them.
感谢上帝
Well, thank god for that.
但是你要知道  不管怎样
But you should be aware that, one way or another,
这种东西总会大白天下的
These sorts of things inevitably see the light of day.
你不喜欢泡沫丰富的吗
Oh, you got something against foamy richness?
对  觉得很讨厌
Yeah.  It annoys me.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
我们核查了霍恩的竞选支出
We cross- referenced Horn's campaign payouts
给博林杰公司的志愿者和雇员的薪水
To the volunteers and employees at Bollinger's office.
然后呢
And?
有一笔总累计3万的支出没记帐
There were a series of off- book payments totaling 30 grand
直接从银行转到银行
Routed bank- to- bank
没有收款人  只有帐号
With no payee, just an account number.
查过了这个帐户吗
Were you able to track down the accounts?
对  是布鲁斯·柯比
Oh, yeah, it's, uh, Bruce Kirby.
那个照相的私家侦探
That P.I. That took the pictures?
他就是那个勒索的人
He is your blackmailer.
查过他了吗
Did you run him up?
当然  好家伙
Of course. A real peach.
使用暴力被警队开除
Lost his badge for excessive force,
刑事恐吓被判缓刑
On probation for criminal intimidation.
根据记录  他有把点38口径的枪
And he has a registration for a .38.
和杀死霍恩议员的枪口径一样
The same caliber that killed councilman Horn.
美味
Oh, that's good.
-好东西  -对
- That's the stuff.  - Yeah.
-好极了  哥们儿  -幸福啊
- It's good, man.  - Flavor country.
对  我有那些照片
Well, I figured I got the photos.
那个胆小鬼不肯用
The gutless punk isn't gonna use 'em.
我为什么不用呢
Why the hell shouldn't I?
因为是违法的
Because it's illegal?
我可不是那个
Hey, I’m not the one that
和小姑娘搞在一起的人
Was dipping my churro in sugar nearly half my age.
他活该的
The guy had it coming.
但他发现了  他找上你了
Except he found you out. He came after you.
对吧
Yeah?
所以是怎么回事  柯比
So what happened, Kirby?
他失控  动手了
He lose his cool, he get violent?
什么  不是的
What? No.
你把他的头打开了花
You put a round in his head
还想嫁祸给克里森
And tried to pin it on Creason.
福尔摩斯  我没杀他
Sherlock, I didn't kill him.
他是来见我
He was coming to meet with me,
是  他有想法的
Yes, with a proposition.
他想知道
He wanted to know what it would take
一笔勾销要多少钱
To make it all go away forever.
你跟他要多少
What did you tell him?
我想  管它的  25万
Well, I thought, what the hell? $250,000.
我可没想过他会同意
I never thought he'd say yes.
他同意了  他有钱
He did, he got the money.
他死的那晚
The night he was killed,
本该带钱来见我的
He was coming to meet me with it.
他没来
He never showed.
你怎么认为
What do you think?
等着从死者那儿拿勒索的钱
Waiting to receive a blackmail payoff from the vic?
我三岁的儿子
My 3-Year-Old son
都能编个更好的故事
Could come up with a better story than that.
话这么说  有可能是实话
It's so bad, it might be true.
我们派了队人在他家找凶器
Yeah, well, we got a team tossing his place for the weapon.
先把他先记在勒索上
Book him on the blackmail
看能找到什么
Till we see what the search turns up.
同时要找出钱在哪里
In the meantime, follow the money.
如果这个蠢蛋说的是真的
If this bozo is telling the truth--
那么霍恩被杀的时候身上有25万
Then Horn had a quarter million when he was killed.
对  钱在哪里
Yeah, so where's the money?
薪水微薄的公务员
And where does an underpaid public servant
能从哪里弄到钱
Get it from in the first place?
他会和其他政客一样
Well, he'd go where all politicians go--
去找喜欢他的人
To people who like him,
以前给过他钱的人
People who gave him money before.
我能回家了吗
Can I go home now?
杰夫·霍恩的离开是一个悲剧
What happened to Jeff Horn was a tragedy...
对他家人如此
Not just for his family,
对他服务过的市民更是如此
But for all of us he served.
尽管暴力夺去了他的生命
And even though violence stole his life,
他的夫人今天来和我们在一起
His wife is here with us today,
不让暴力夺去他的梦想
Refusing to let violence steal his dream
创造更好的纽约
Of a better New York.
女士们先生们  劳里·霍恩
Ladies and gentlemen, Laurie Horn.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
我们都知道
We all know
今天本应是我丈夫在这里讲话
It should be my husband speaking with you today.
本应是他沉着的声音
It should be his calming voice,
不是大家现在听到我的声音
Not mine, that you hear.
这是市议员竞选  不是美国参议院竞选
This is a city council race, not the U.S. Senate.
我们靠的是成百上千的小额捐款
We rely on thousands of small donations,
不是几个大富翁
Not a few big ones.
他们的某些人财力雄厚
Well, some of them must have deep pockets.
捐助的额度受法律限制
Well, the depth of those pockets is limited by the law.
如果没有法律限制
And if it wasn't limited by law,
霍恩的支持者
Did Horn have any supporters
会不会多捐一些呢
That would be willing to go the extra mile?
探长  恕我直言
Detective...with all due respect,
我根本不可能
There's no way in hell
帮助你们
I'm helping you start a witch hunt
迫害我们的重要捐赠人
Against our top supporters.
你们想调查我们的竞选捐赠人
Now you want to go through our campaign contributors?
没问题  记录都是公开的
Fine. That's a matter of public record.
但是其它的事情  你们自己想办法吧
But anything else, and you're on your own.
-这边  -谢谢
- Over this way! - Thank you. Yes.
-作业写完了  -是的
- Finished your homework? - Yeah.
-你能帮我做完工作么  -要看情况而定
- You wanna finish mine? - Well, that depends.
你能付我多少报酬
How much are you offering to pay me?
得到我的真传了
Oh, I taught you well.
吉娜来过电话
Gina called.
她让我提醒你
She wanted me to remind you
签书会和朗诵会
About the reading and book signing
明晚在百老汇出版社
At Broadway Books tomorrow night.
真谢谢她了
Well, that was nice of her.
如果你不露面  她就要
Yeah, and if you don't show, she will...
在你眼珠上滴上蜂蜜
"Drip honey on your eyeballs
然后放上一大堆的火蚁
And let loose a hundred fire ants."
好  哪个更糟
Okay. What's worse--
数以百计的火蚁在你眼珠上
A hundred fire ants on your eyeballs
还是给一群人读书
Or reading to a crowd...
如此糟糕的文章
"Prose so bad
足以让我尖叫着冲进风雪中
It sent me screaming out into the snow"?
你知道的  如果你真想为自己难过
You know, if you really want to feel sorry for yourself,
你应该读帐簿网的评论
You should read the review in "the Ledger."
真的  这该死的自由精英媒体
Really? What's that damn liberal elite media
都是怎么说我的
Saying about me now?
理查德·卡塞尔那激动人心的大结局
"Richard Castle's stirring finale
让我们领略低俗小说的精妙
Reminds us what good pulp fiction is all about".
令我们向往那惊奇而不完美的世界
"It makes us desire a world of startling imperfection
所以我们克服困难
So we can rise above
并且成为我们
And become the heroes
自己理想的英雄
We always imagined ourselves to be."
这报纸以前办得不错
It used to be such a good paper.
看到它这么堕落  真让人伤心
To see it fallen so far, it's sad, really.
别说了
Shut up.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
等下次  我在你朋友面前唱花生酱时
Well, you remember that next time
你要记得你说过这话
I sing the peanut butter song in front of your friends.
你们抓到凶手了吗
Have you caught the killer yet?
没有
No.
如果你遇到大麻烦
Hey, if you were in a lot of trouble
而且  还需要25万美元
And you needed a quarter of a million dollars,
你会从哪里弄钱
Where would you get it?
我会向你要
I'd just ask you.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night.  - Good night.
我会向你要
I'd just ask you.
我要给你看样东西
There's something I need to show you.
我在他第一次竞选的档案里发现了这个
I found this in the archives from his first run for office.
霍恩当时没有钱  但他妻子家境富裕
See, Horn wasn't wealthy, but his wife came from money.
她用自己家的信托基金
She tapped into her family trust
来资助他的首次竞选
To finance his first campaign.
我们一直以为
All this time we thought that
霍恩向妻子瞒住了外遇
Horn was hiding his affair from his wife.
是的  但是假如她已经知道这件事
Yeah, but what if she knew about the affair?
倘若他向她伸手要赎款呢
What if he got the blackmail money from her?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
账号是737-88103  谢谢
Account number 737-88103. Thanks.
据家庭信托基金的经纪人所说
According to the administrator of the family trust,
霍恩夫人上周
Mrs. Horn marketed
出售了大约30万美元的股票
About $300,000 worth of stocks last week.
她早知道
She knew.
银行记录显示
Bank records indicate
这笔钱在交易的前两天被提出
The funds were withdrawn two days before the exchange.
她丈夫被杀  二十五万美元不翼而飞
Her husband's killed, $250,000 goes missing,
她却不声不响
She doesn't say a word?
我确实没说
Of course I didn't say a word.
这些跟你们无关
It's none of your damn business.
即便可能
Despite the fact that it could have had
与你丈夫的死有重大关系
Significant bearing on your husband's murder?
我还有孩子  贝克特探长
I have a family, detective Beckett.
他们的父亲已经死了
Their father is dead.
还要把这个作为午夜脱口秀的笑料
What use is dragging their names through the mud,
让孩子们名誉扫地吗
Providing fodder for late- night comedians?
你是什么时候知道的
When did you know?
信托来电确认股票交易
The trust called to confirm the stock sale.
我那好丈夫在文件上模仿我的签名
My wonderful husband forged my signature on the papers,
以为我会笨的发现不了
Thinking I would be too stupid to notice,
当我与他对质的时候
And when I confronted him,
他说由于税务方面的原因需要这些钱
He claimed he needed the money for tax reasons,
一些我不懂的原因
Reasons that I wouldn't understand.
但是  我还是明白了
But I understood, all right.
我想要的一切
Everything that I wanted,
我想要的将来
Everything that I wanted us to be,
但他不能克制自己的欲望
And he can't keep his fly zipped.
那么你是决定怎么做的
So what did you decide to do?
在当众羞辱和被敲诈之间
Well, between public humiliation and blackmail,
我选择被敲诈
I chose blackmail,
我告诉他把事情解决了
And I told him make it go away.
你觉得那天晚上发生了什么
So what do you think happened that night?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧  那么当晚他给你打电话时
Okay. So that night, when he called,
他到底都说了些什么
What did he actually say?
说他拿到了钱  准备去见那个家伙
That he had the money, that he was going to meet the guy,
这就是最后  他对我说的话
And that was the last thing he said to me.
老天知道后来发生了什么
And god knows what happened after that.
你确定钱在他手上
And you're sure that he had the money?
是的  怎么了
Yes. Why?
因为我们在你家发现了这笔钱
Because we found it at your house.
我家
My house.
今天早上拿到的搜查证
The search warrant was served this morning.
你的管家非常合作
Your housekeeper was very cooperative.
如果你丈夫被杀时身上带着钱
If your husband had the money when he was killed,
这笔钱怎么又跑回你家
How did it get back to your house?
你何止是生气  不是吗
You were more than angry, weren’t you?
简直是愤怒至极
You were outraged.
他不仅背叛你  还令你蒙羞
He didn't just betray you, he humiliated you.
而每个人都会知道
And everyone was going to know,
所以你就决定  做个了断
And so you just decided to...make it go away.
看到那些无法逃避新闻发布会的妻子们
You see those wives in the inevitable press conference,
面无表情的站在她们丈夫的身边
Standing stone-Faced next to their men,
你会想  她们怎么做到的
And you think, how do they do that?
她们怎么能就只站在那里
How do they just stand there?
眼睁睁看着
How do they watch
自己的世界
As their whole world
在聚光灯下  在羞耻中土崩瓦解
Melts into a spotlight of shame?
所以你杀了他
And so you killed him.
不  我当时在家
N-No. N-No. I-I was home.
你晚上11点给你丈夫打电话说了什么
You called your husband at 11:00 P.M. What did you say?
我当时和女儿们在一起
I-I-I was with my daughters.
无论你是否在现场
Conspiracy to commit murder is the same as murder,
同谋与谋杀犯的性质一样
Whether you were there or not.
准备坦白吗
Are you ready to deal?
我要做的只是打电话
It was my job to make the call.
我只要告诉他
I was supposed to tell him
敲诈的人改变了见面地点
That the blackmailer changed the meet.
然后告诉他怎么走
I was supposed to tell him where to go--
从那个没人能看到的地下通道下去
Down by the underpass where no one would see.
他已经安排好了一切
He had it all arranged,
甚至连裹尸毯都准备了
Even that rug for his body.
我要做的只是打一通电话
All I had to do was make a call.
他说他会处理现场
He said he would make everything like it was.
弄得像别人干的
He said he would make it look like someone else did it.
他还说没有人会知道
He said no one would ever know.
霍恩夫人
Mrs. Horn...
劳里  我要知道这人是谁
Laurie, I need to know who.
不应该是这样的
It's not supposed to be like this.
我们是朋友
We were friends...
我们要改变世界
And we were gonna change the world.
弗兰克·内斯比特
Frank Nesbit,
你因谋杀杰夫·霍恩被捕了
You are under arrest for the murder of Jeff Horn.
什么  荒谬
What? That's ridiculous.
霍恩夫人可不这么想  铐上他
Mrs. Horn doesn't think so. Cuff him.
内斯比特先生  你有权保持沉默  任何
Mr. Nesbit, you have the right to remain silent. Any--
老兄  别跑了  竞选结束了
Stop running, bro. The campaign's over.
哦  是啊
Ooh. Yes.
我还没有说完呢  内斯比特先生
I wasn't quite finished back there, Mr. Nesbit.
你有权保持沉默  你所说的话
You have the right to remain silent. Anything you say can
将会成为呈堂证供
And will be used against you in a court of law.
在内斯比特的办公室找到凶器之后
After we found the weapon in Nesbit's office,
他交代了全过程
He made a full confession.
他让霍恩给她的丈夫打电话
He got Horn to call her husband
然后让他下了天桥
And get him down to the overpass,
剩下的事情都由他处理了
And then he took care of the rest.
政治是内斯比特的生命
Politics was Nesbit's life.
他说过  如果绯闻传出去
He figured if the scandal broke,
他的职业生涯就结束了
His career would be over,
他会被毁了
And he'd be damaged goods.
可悲的是  他或许是对的
The sad thing is, he was probably right.
那么两个女孩怎么样了
So what happens to the girls?
霍恩有个姐姐在纽约北部
Horn had a sister upstate.
她明天到
She's coming down tomorrow
把孩子们从社会服务中心接走
To pick 'em up from social services.
好的  毯子呢
Good. And the rug?
障眼法
A red herring.
内斯比特听说他们扔掉一大堆毯子
Nesbit heard they were dumping a bunch of 'em,
认为这样可以引开我们
Figured it would keep us off his trail.
做的好  真不错
Nice work. Very impressive.
你也不错  贝克特
Oh, and, uh, you, too, Beckett.
长官
Sir?
逗你玩儿的  探长
Just yanking your chain, detective.
逗你玩儿呢
Just yanking your chain.
你好
Hello.
老爸  你在哪呢
Hey, dad, where are you?
我应该在哪里
Where am I supposed to be?
火蚁  眼球
Fire ants? Eyeballs?
对了  帮我拖住她  我马上到
Right. Uh, stall for me. I'm on my way.
对不起  对不起
Oops!  Sorry. Sorry.
她惊呆了  站在那里
"She stood there in stunned disbelief"
当他眼里的光逐渐黯淡
"As the light in his eyes dimmed."
他向她伸出手  她伸手握住
"He reached out for her, and she took his hand,"
最后一次  紧紧握住
"Squeezing it for the very last time."
她感到心脏漏了一拍
"She felt her heart stop a beat,"
那一瞬间
"And in that moment,"
她知道他走了
"She knew he was gone."
黑暗掠过整个城市的面庞
"Darkness fell across the face of the city"
掠过她的面庞
"And across her face as well."
很好  当风拢起她的头发  她想着
"Good, she thought, as the wind gathered up her hair."
没有谁
"No one..."
会看见我的眼泪
"Will see my tears."
谢谢
Thank you. Uh...
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
什么风把你吹来了
To what do I owe this very unexpected pleasure?
失陪  谢谢
Excuse me. Thank you.
我只是想  你打搅我的工作
I just figured if you're gonna bother me at my work,
在你工作时候  我也要烦你
I should bother you at yours.
朗诵得真不错
That was, um, quite a reading.
非常感人
Very, uh, moving.
你是在嘲笑我吗
Are--Are you making fun of me?
很好  当风拢起她的头发  她想着
"Good, she thought, as the wind gathered up her hair."
没有谁会看到我的眼泪
"No one will see my tears."
我很好奇  风怎么能拢起头发呢
How does wind gather up hair? I'm just curious.
你是在告诉我该怎么工作吗
Oh, you're telling me how to do my job.
很烦人  是吗
Irritating, isn't it?
看看你们俩
Look at you.
帐簿网的丹尼斯说
Denise from "the Ledger" says
你这本书将是本周的销量冠军
You're going to be number one this week.
看看  所有人都在买你的书
And look, everyone is buying your book!
现在不觉得相信那些评论很愚蠢吗
Now don't you feel silly for believing all those reviews?
是的  很蠢
Yes. Yes, I do.
希望妮奇·希特也能大卖
Let's just hope "Nikki Heat" does as well.
妮奇·希特
"Nikki Heat"?
这个角色以你为原型
The character he's basing on you.
-妮奇·希特   -糟糕
- Nikki Heat?  - Uh-Oh.
借一步说话可以吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
当然
Of course.
-让他去  让他去  -我想听听
- Let him. Let him. - I want to hear.
妮奇·希特  算个什么名字
What kind of a name is Nikki Heat?
一位警官的名字
A cop name.
是脱衣舞娘的名字
It's a stripper name.
我告诉过你  她有点放荡
Well, I told you she was kind of slutty.
把名字换了  卡塞尔
Change it, Castle.
等等  想想这些书名
Wait. Hang on a second. Think of the titles--
酷夏  热浪
"Summer heat," "heat wave,"
纵情
"In heat."
把这名字改掉
Change the name.
-不  -改掉
- No. - Yes.
-不改  -改掉
- No. - Change it.
-不  -卡塞尔
- No. - Castle.
-我不是想说  -对不起
- I'm not speaking... - Sorry.
我要保持作品的艺术上完整性  贝克特
I have artistic integrity,  Beckett.
艺术上的完整性
"Artistic integrity"?
卡塞尔  今天就把名字换了
Change the name, Castle! Today.